(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T22:09:59.232180",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team friends, team friends
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team friends
関西 関東 西 東、北南 チーム友達
Kansai, Kanto, West, East, North, South, team friends
チーム友達 チーム友達 チーム友達 チーム友達
Team friends, team friends, team friends, team friends
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team friends, team friends
チーム チーム チーム友達
Team, team, team friends
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team friends
お好み焼き 食う 鶴橋
Okonomiyaki eating in Tsuruhashi
腹いっぱい 飯は美味い
A full meal is delicious
一人じゃ寂しいし電話したり
If I'm lonely, I'll call someone
かけ直した後すぐ行く会いに
And go see them right after calling back
t e a m t o m o d a c h i
チーム友達 チーム友達 混ざり合い
Team friends, team friends, mixing together
契り交わし 飲んでる酒
Exchanging pledges, drinking wine
契り 契り 契り 契り
Pledge, pledge, pledge, pledge
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's pledge, let's pledge, let's pledge, let's pledge
契り 契り 契り 契り
Pledge, pledge, pledge, pledge
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's pledge, let's pledge, let's pledge, let's pledge
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team friends, team friends
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team friends
関西 関東 西 東、北南 北南 チーム友達
Kansai, Kanto, West, East, North, South, team friends
チーム友達 チーム友達 チーム友達
Team friends, team friends, team friends
チーム チーム チーム友達
Team, team, team friends
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team friends
チーム友達 チーム友達 チーム友達 チーム友達
Team friends, team friends, team friends, team friends
You know, come to think of it, it's been two years since we broke out of the cell, huh?
Yeah, time goes by fast.
We've been through a lot, right?
Attention, Justice. Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Initiating final warning protocol. 5 escapees detected from the cell.
Repeat, 5 escapees detected from the cell. Targets are as follows:
The Demon of Sound, Nerissa Ravencroft.
The Jewel of Emotion, Koseki Bijou.
The Fluffy One, Fuwawa Abyssgard.
The Fuzzy One, Mococo Abyssgard.
The Archivist, Shiori Novella.
All units, apprehend the Advent members immediately.
Oh, oh, oh! We're in trouble! It's the feds, baby!
Oh, wait! They're catching me!
What are you doing?
Piggyback ride, come on! Piggyback ride!
Wait, guys! Think, there's got to be a solution for this, right?
Piggyback ride! Come on! Piggyback ride! Piggyback ride!
Bwahaha! Struggling already?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Ask nicely enough, and maybe I'll save your skins.
Or I'll punch you forever! Come on, come on!
Okay, um... here, please. I have a solution.
Don't race so fast, Pokey!
Hmph! I don't hate that.
If you manage to pass the little trial I've cooked up for you, I'll whisk you away to a whole other realm... one where your pesky pursuers can't reach you!
I mean, I guess that's our only option, huh? I guess so.
What if we don't have a license? Whistle, whistle, the people seem stopped.
Yeah, interesting. I like that.
See this course? Time to tackle the 'Go-Kart Escape Challenge'!
Escape? Escaping? Escaping!
Yes, that's right. Take it from here, ankle-biter.
How are you talking to, huh? Who are you calling ankle-biter?
Calm down there. Well, actually, all right, team! Game rules are incoming, so make sure you better listen, okay?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Shiori, Shiori, give me give me give me.
Yeah! Oh, cool, nice!
Wait, Bijou, how do you know the game rules? Isn't it like—
It's the glasses. That's how she knows.
Rule 1: Survive 2 laps with zombies on your tail!
Zombies?
Where? Wait, remember last year we beat up zombies?
Well, one of them went like on a path to revenge and now it's going to run out to you.
Okay, Pokey.
Rule 2: Collect items for bonus points, but watch out for traps that deduct points!
Oh, no! Traps that deduct points!
Rule 3: Victory is ours if we all get 30 points total!
Easy, right? 30 points total!
And now I will explain the course items—
I must run! She must be where people go.
I'm going to live out my dreams while there's a track here. Just explain, ignore me, ignore me! Okay, hey, hey.
There are— Oh, she's so fat!
Ignore me! There are— There are crystals on the field! And the people crystal over there! And—
Two more over there. They are gotcha!
You either gain points or lose points based on...
But you don't know, so it's a risk every time.
Yeah. And then, there is the big Moai.
The big Moai!
It will block your path.
It is minus 20 points if you hit it, so don't hit it.
And then, the pebble!
I have kidnapped one of my pebbles to use as a sacrifice. If you hit it, minus 5 points, but you know what, I don't think...
Think with mine, if you hit it. To be honest.
And the items will change, depending on
your first lap or second lap. You're doing two laps.
Two laps? Are we too many? You can run another two laps?
Yeah. Are you okay? Yeah, I'm great.
I guess, time to show you how it's done. Show us! Go on, go on!
All right, first lap. Show us how to do it.
3, 2, 1, Go!
Oh, first lap, first lap, crystal! She gets a crystal, she makes a move.
Second crystal! Watch out! Moai!
She scores plus 5 pts! Oh, zombies are just speeding up. Second lap, let's go, let's go!
Another crystal! She hit another one. Watch out!
Oh, why are you... The zombies! Help! She's gonna hit the Moai! Watch out, don't be a stone.
Don't be a stone! They cut you. She's hit the fire! Yeah!
I think you got a bit of bad luck with that crystal at the end. It's okay, it's also a pretty good run.
That's so fast! You almost hit the zombie, but you're okay. It's okay.
You didn't die! How many points did I get? How many points?
That's a good question. How many points did you get? How many points did I get? I think you got one point.
What? One point? Oh, it was all negative! One point? What did I do? Did I have bad gacha luck?
It's okay! It's still a group effort, we can still get points. Yeah, I can, two is fine.
One is great, one is great! You can let like the pro do all the work for you, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Pro, go, go, go! Yeah, yeah, I'll go to you guys.
Okay, next up is... Nerissa! Show us how it's done, our fearless leader.
I have a plan. What's your plan? You'll figure it out when I say plan.
Good luck, Shiorin! Ano, ano, zombie-ra saki do zo.
Good luck, Shiorin! Um, zombies, go ahead.
Hey! What? You go this way, you go this way!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Yeah, let's get it. Touch me da zo.
Hit right there, don't wanna get away. Oh, watch out for the Moai! Watch out for the Moai!
Yeah, you got a plus 5 pt! Yeah, yeah, yeah, keep on going. It's like driving in New York!
Only thing is... Ah, that's okay, I can figure it out. How do you get away?
Okay, okay, okay. You can get the bigger crystal now. Oh, hit the fire, minus 3 pts! You didn't catch him, but you sure gave him a run for his money!
I forgot about the points. I just wanted to run them over. Understandable. How did we do? It's okay, how many points did you get?
Shiori's points: 3 pts! That's it, I'm running you over. That's two points to the point. That's pretty good. That's better than one.
So, we have four... All right, it's up to time!
Do you think you can do it? I'll get four more points. You can do it, I know you can. That's for sure. The zombie is not gonna run away anymore, so...
Yeah, I think it's tired. It's up to you, you can outrun...
3, 2, 1, Go!
Oh, no! Your cart is going slow. What do you mean? I want to go the fast way. Oh, you got the crystal! Very safe driving.
It's okay. The zombie's taking their time too.
Wait, is it the first lap?
No, maybe?
Oh, no!
I can do it! Okay, okay!
Go, go, go, go! Go, Fuwawa! Go, Fuwawa!
Why is it so slow this time?
Pump pump!
Ah, the crystal, the crystal! Oh yeah!
Watch out! Watch out! Oh, I'm dead!
Yay! Oh, she finished her lap.
Is it the first lap still? This is the second one now.
Okay, okay, I can do it! I can do it!
Ah, fluff me!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go! Ah, I can do it! Oh, no!
You can do it! I can do it! Oh, what is this?
Hold strong! Ah, I can do it!
Okay, okay! Yay!
Pump pump! Yay! I guess the speed isn't that important, but the points are right? Yeah!
Pump pump! Yay! Speed isn't everything, but the points are right? Yeah!
Bau Bau! Fuwawa, I think you did really well! Ah, yeah!
So far, you're our top performer today with 18 points!
Fuwawa's carry! Don't worry, we're at 18!
I asked - how much? Fuwawa's was 17? 18!
I asked—how much? Fuwawa's was 17? 18!
14, 18. You got three, and you got one, so yeah.
14, 18. No, no, we got 44 points!
44 points! Okay!
Let's go, Fuwawa! Count on me, Fuwawa! Keep going, Fuwawa!
You got this, Mococo!
Mococo, go! Yay! I'll be offensive eventually.
It's a slow burn!
Ah, fluff me! Oh, no!
Watch out! Watch out! Watch out! Watch out!
I can't hear you! I can't hear you! I can do this, Mococo!
1, 2, 3! Yay! Walking kid!
Mococo, go, go, go, go!
Pump pump! Yay! Mococo, you can do it! Mococo!
How did you - huh? Ah, you did really great!
How did you—huh? Ah, you did really great!
So we should never catch me. I think with you, we have enough.
So you should never catch me. I think with you, we have enough.
Yeah, you got 12 points!
12 points! Plus 18, that's 30, right? Mococo high-five! High-five! Yay!
I can't get negative points. You can't get negative points? Still up to you.
Don't listen to anything. Negative points! You're not going to ruin it for us.
Well, you know what guys? I have a driver's license, so I'm not worried about this at all.
Better than all of us. Don't listen to her. This test is about zombies, huh?
I'm not scared of zombies! That's what you say now.
I'm not scared! (3, 2, 1, GO!)
Wait, so start.
Watch out! Watch out! Watch out! And necklace!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Uh-oh! Uh-oh! I can do this!
Watch out!
I have a license! I can do this!
Second lap! Second lap! Drifting!
Look at her! I'm not going to go!
I can do this!
Watch out! Watch out! Careful, Advent!
I don't know if that went well, but I feel like I probably did better than you guys still.
Wait, you can get negative points!
I only spun out three times.
Yeah, you spun out three times. When you spin out, it's not allowed.
Well, what are my points?
What did you say? 34?
You got 9 points.
No! 39!
That means we passed, right? That means we passed!
High-five! We did it! High-five!
We did it! Good job, Nerissa!
What do you say, huh? Yeah, did we get our deal?
Not bad!
As promised, interdimensional travel! All aboard!
Get in and go!
Wow, what a ride! But let's crash it.
No, I have a better idea. What idea?
Let's make a music video!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin’ life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
’Cause this is where my story all begins
Livin’ it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy
I can’t get enough
Free as a bird, no limit
Haven’t you heard? I’m fearless
Get up and go, let’s do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me be your diva
I’m gonna raise your fever
Shakin’ up all the crowd
Making some noise when I’m not allowed
Livin’ my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my every whim
Don’t blame me if I shine too bright
Can’t help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention, please
’Cause this is only the beginning
It’s our genesis
Coming to wreak some havoc
How do you like this plot twist?
I’m embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I’m destined for great things
I’m sure you’ve heard of me by now
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I’m mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
Gonna start the rave when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I’m gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken, the rules can all be broken
I’m running on a rampage, the world is a blank page
I’m writing my story in flames and in glory
They’re gonna know me by name
Is this my promised land?
The future’s in my hands
But they don’t understand
That I’m a star in the making, awaking and taking a bow
Tell me, how you like me now?
Come and watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control, ready?
You’ve got to free your mind, leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is, it’s our genesis
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin’ life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
’Cause this is our beginning, it’s our genesis
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I’m destined for great things
I’m sure you’ve heard of me by now
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I’m mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
You know what time it is? It’s our genesis
Tell me what time it is, It’s our genesis
Yeah, you know what time it is? It’s our genesis
Oh, this is nice.
Yeah, I like it. It feels nice and breathable.
I want to see everyone close up, though. This is our first time wearing something like this, so...
Say, Juubee, won't you show off what you've got on, at least first? Okay?
Uh, what are you looking at, huh?
If you're looking at fine, you can look a little bit, okay?
Here we go. It's my skirt. Do you like the skirt?
Ah, it's so sparkly! You're like highlighters!
Kida-Kida, I'm gonna blind you!
Oh, my god! Don't let me talk to her!
Just look at her! Just look at her!
Forward! Take over! Go, go, post your stories!
Is this kind of my first bathing suit, boy?
Ah, what do you think?
Tail's fluffier than normal!
Oh boy, oh boy, yeah!
Shiori, come here!
Shiori-no-shoin-shoin-no-shoin-oh!
Shiori-no-shoin-shoin-at-your-service!
And look at my little ribbon!
Mococo, you can do this, Mococo!
Bow wow, bow wow, ah!
Mococo, you can do this, you can do it!
Tail is so big, tail is so cute!
Look at those cute shorts!
She's so cute, Mococo, you can do this, Mococo!
Rissa, don't leave us!
Yes! But there's something a bit special on this outfit, don't you think? If you go down...
Oh, there it is! There it is! Wow, is that too much?
Don't look there too much, but if you come up...
You can see my waist, and my armpits, yes, the pits!
But I see something strange off in the distance. Just wait, let me go see.
Oh, it's a selfie stick!
Everyone get behind me!
Let's take a picture together!
Why are you so ho— Why are you so tall?
Oh, that helps!
There's something down there in the sand.
I think that's an Eventrix! Let's step on it! Careful! Careful! Yeah!
Let's go to the water!
Don't fall down! Don't drown! Run in slow-mo!
Let's, let's just keep running on the beach!
I want to touch the water! Let's touch the water! Wait, don't touch the water yet! Ah, let's stop!
Somebody go put this thing down, okay? Oh, my arms are getting tired.
Selfie arm tired! Selfie arm losing it!
Thank you for being such a helpful person.
Oh my gosh, it's Pokey!
Hey now! Save the beach party for later!
Sandcastles later, survival now! They already detected your dimension jump.
I thought we were supposed to be safe here!
What the world is this? Hey, can we swim, do leisure, and enjoy our time?
This is Justice we're dealing with! Expect the unexpected!
What should we do next then? Will we have to run forever?
Don't panic, I have a plan. Prove your bonds in the next trial, and I may assist you.
The power of friendship! Nakama power!
Wait, this is the beach episode! And we have to run with sand!
Good. Something's been arranged. Look down! A & B!
A and B? Look at our outfits! That's so lame!
C-Can it! Silence! To confirm your bonds, you'll take on "Master of Advent."
Master of Advent
[Title: Master of Advent]
Each participant will be asked a two-option question related to Advent.
You guys are Team Tomodachi, so it should be pretty easy, right..?
Yeah! We are Team Tomodachi!
Exactly. But incorrect answers mean... your bonds are weak, so I prepared a penalty game!
Yeah, a penalty game. Now, goth girl, take over.
Anyway, I think that we're going to get one question, two answers, but only one is right. And if you get it wrong, unfortunately, I think you're going to get muddied.
Oh! What do you mean by get muddied?
Yeah, I don't want to get muddy in this thing!
So when you make your answer, I want you to hop there, okay? O-Okay. Choose, choose, choose.
Okay, I'll go first as an example, okay? Okay.
Number one. Would Shiori rather be a vampire for A, or a werewolf for B?
And count of three, okay? Three, two...
1, go!
One, go!
I don't want to drink blood! What am I, stupid?
That's unexpected.
I seriously thought you were going to say vampire.
No, you got that dog in you. You soul, I got that dog in me, yeah.
Wait, I said A by mistake! I didn't want A! No!
What if you could?
You too. I'm watching you.
Well, you got us all wet, Shiori. Are you happy?
Not yet.
All right.
Next one, how about Mococo?
Mococo's turn!
Okay, wow. Here I go! Um, at the beach...
When I rather collect seashells, A,
or, um, how was it? Ah, make sandcastles, B.
Okay, here we go. Ready?
Okay. Jump on three.
Three, two, one.
Which was what?
I can't remember.
This was seashells, and this was sandcastles.
You're getting dirty!
Yeah! It's Shiori! No, I thought you wanted this one.
I made a mistake!
I want to collect seashells, but jump this way, so not this way, this way.
Shiori, safe for now. Yeah, for now, for now.
How was fun?
That is so mean!
Seriously, it was a game of tag.
How about Fuwawa next?
I don't get to get dirty this time, right? Yeah.
Okay, my question.
Do I prefer long-haired cats or short-haired cats?
And the fluffy one. Both of them.
Here we go. Three, two, one.
No way!
What? You prefer short hair? Are you supposed to love it?
It's too easy! It's a trick question.
It's too obvious!
You're so mean to me!
You're so close to the hair.
Make you boil!
Ah, that feels nice.
What's going to be your turn next?
No, sister, come back!
I don't want to! I don't want to play this game anymore. It's too mechanic.
Okay, is it Bijou's turn now?
It's Bijou's turn now! Okay.
My question is, oh, okay.
Would I rather fight one hundred chicken-sized hippopotamuses on A,
or one hippopotamus-sized chicken on B? Do you understand?
No, I don't understand!
One hundred hippo... one hundred chicken-sized hippos... I mean, you know, one hippo-sized chicken.
I'm not repeating it!
Oh, this this is a single one. Okay.
Okay, ready and
three, two, one.
Bijou doesn't like ads! Bijou likes boss battles! You should have known! It's boss battles!
You have a milk with the question...
「そう、始まるわよ！」
"So it finally begins!"
「残念ながら、あなたたちは…」
"Unfortunately for you—"
「ほら、もうすぐ。ほら、もうすぐ来るよ。来るよ、来るよ、スティが」
"Look, soon. Look, it's coming soon. Here it comes, here comes the Sti—"
「待って、待って、待って！　あなた、あなた…」
"Wait, wait, wait! You, you—"
「あなたたちには1チャンスを。さあ、慈悲を…」
"You guys get one chance. Now, have mercy..."
「慈悲？　ゲットソリッド！」
"Mercy? Get sollied!"
「待って！　私だけソリッド？」
"Wait! Only me sollied?!"
「どうして、私だけこんなの？　どうして、どうして？　オッケー？　ノー！」
"Why is it only me like this? Why, why? Okay? No!"
「バイバイ、私行くからね。バイバイ、バイバイ、バイバイ…」
"Bye-bye, I'm going. Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye..."
"Your turn now!"
"She became a mermaid. She's swimming away. We'll never see her again."
"Come back, Mococo! We need you!"
"I am a maid now!"
"Oh, my. Oh, my!"
"Last is my turn, which means I can't get it wrong, which feels pretty good."
"Uhm, what's a good question? I'm not really sure. Uhm, let's see."
"Nerissa is a demon, but she's also half raven."
"If I had to pick between worlds and either be just a demon or just a raven..."
"So demon is B, raven is A. Which would I pick?"
"Alright. Yes, okay. On three, okay?"
"1, 2, 3!"
"Oh! I told you, you would never give up laying eggs."
"I can't lay eggs! That's not the case!"
"I just think it would be great if I could have powers that aren't dependent on— something that can break, you know?"
"I thought being a demon is cooler, though."
"You know what is? Wait, being a demon— You know what is even cooler than being a demon?"
"You know what's even cooler than being a demon, Shiori and Mococo? What? I dare you!"
"I dare you! I dare you! I'm being covered in mud!"
"Yeah, there you go! Don't call me cock for you!"
"Yeah, you want to call me cock for you?"
"I like baths, so it's okay."
"Yeah, you like that? Well, you like it so much, go take one in the ocean."
"Go into the ocean! Go into the ocean!"
"That's probably going like this."
"Well, we'll never see them again. Uh-oh, they're getting lost in the water. I think they're having too much fun digging up the sea. But, uh, it's fine. Don't eat the salt water."
"Yeah, don't drink the water! Blub, blub, blub, blub, blub..."
"I'm digging up the beach. I'm digging up the beach."
"I'm going to get rid of this."
"That was pretty funny. Did we win? I feel like I won."
"Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! That didn't go so well, huh? Look how dirty you are!"
"But hey, idols don't give up that easy, right? You are idols, right? Let's turn this around and shine again!"
"And if you do... I'll take you somewhere super special— where even Justice can't find us!"
"Wait, what? We're not solied! We got a little conflicted. I want Justice to find me at some point."
"Well, we can go! Okay, just for now, just for now!"
"Let's go to the ocean! Let's go to the ocean!"
どこどこそこも 見つからないぜ
"You won't find it anywhere!"
パパイヤ マンゴー ココ☆ナツ
"Papaya, mango, Coco☆Natsu!"
かき氷 イチゴ味 ベロを出したら
"Shaved ice, strawberry flavor, if you stick out your tongue,"
真っ赤っか!
"it's bright red!"
もうすぐサン・サン・水・SHOW! SAY! ジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
"Soon it's Sun Sun Water SHOW! SAY! Ta-da-da-da-da-da-da!"
ココナッツ! iei!
"Coconut! Yay!"
カチカチに燃えているおひさま
"The sun is burning fiercely hot,"
待ちわびた季節はサマー・サマー
"the long-awaited season is summer, summer!"
思い切って買っちゃった ビキニ
"I went all out and bought a bikini!"
すっごく照れるけど 負けない!!
"I'm super embarrassed, but I won't lose!"
日焼け止めココナッツ全員集合
"Sunscreen, coconut, everyone gather around!"
待ちわびた季節はサマー・サマー
"the long-awaited season is summer, summer!"
紫外線とココナッツレイザービーム
"Ultraviolet rays and coconut laser beams!"
待ちわびた季節はサマー・サマー どっきゅーん ずっきゅーん
"the long-awaited season is summer, summer! Thump, thumping!"
キミの視線 心臓 大爆発☆
"Your gaze— heart explosion!"
サシセセ ココナッツ ペイベイ
"Sa-shi-se-se coconut, hey baby!"
ダディデュデ どこなつ？ ペイベイ
"Da-di-du-de, where's Natsu? Hey baby!"
かきくけ ココナッツ ペイベイ
"Ka-ki-ku-ke coconut, hey baby!"
サン・サン・サマータイム！ イエス！
"Sun, sun, summertime! Yes!"
どこ？そこ？あそこ？
Where? There? Over there?
見つからないぜぃ？
Can't find it anywhere?
パパイア マンゴー ココ☆ナツ！
Papaya, mango, coconut!
かき氷 イチゴ味
Shaved ice, strawberry flavor,
ベロを出せばまっかっか！ai！
Stick out your tongue and it's all red! Ai!
猛暑 残暑 水着show！say！
Intense heat, late summer heat, swimsuit show! Say!
ココ☆ナツ いえい
Coco☆Nuts, yeah!
カチカチに燃えてるおひさま
The sun is burning fiercely,
ぱっしゅぱっしゅ ココ☆ナツ ベイビー
Splash, splash, Coco☆Nuts, baby!
待ちわびた季節はサマーサマー
The season we've waited for is summer, summer!
思い切って買っちゃったビキニ
I took the plunge and bought a bikini!
すっごーく照れるけど負けない！！
I'm super embarrassed, but I won't lose!!
日焼け止め ココナツフレイバー
Sunscreen with a coconut flavor,
ぱっしゅぱっしゅ ココ☆ナツ ベイビー
Splash, splash, Coco☆Nuts, baby!
紫外線 トコナツレイザー
Ultraviolet rays, tropical laser,
ぱっしゅぱっしゅ ココ☆ナツ ベイビー
Splash, splash, Coco☆Nuts, baby!
どっきゅーんずっきゅーん キミの視線
Dokyuun, zukyuun, your gaze—
心臓大爆発☆
Heart exploding into a big bang!
サシスケソ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-ke-so, Soco-nuts, baby!
ダディデュデド どこなつ？ べいべー
Da-di-du-de-do, Doko-nuts? Baby!
かきくけココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke, Coco-nuts, baby!
サン！サン！サマータイム！yes！！！
Sun! Sun! Summer time! Yes!!!
待ちわびた季節はサマーサマー
The season we've waited for is summer, summer!
長ーい夜で
Long nights and...
短いサマータイム
A short summer time!
やっちゃったもんがち！
Whatever you do, you take what you can get!
サシスケソ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-ke-so, Soco-nuts, baby!
ダディデュデド どこなつ？ べいべー
Da-di-du-de-do, Doko-nuts? Baby!
かきくけココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke, Coco-nuts, baby!
サン！サン！サマータイム！yes！！！
Sun! Sun! Summer time! Yes!!!
ファイヤー！
Fire!
スススパークリング！
Super sparkling!
リリリリリリンボー！
Li-li-li-li-li-limbo!
フィーバー！
Fever!
ソイヤソイヤソイヤソイヤ！
Saiya, saiya, saiya, saiya!
アチアチのサマー 九十九里浜
Hot, hot summer, Kujukurihama!
アイス激アマ
Ice, super sweet!
キャンプはさいたま
Camping in Saitama!
サシスケソ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-ke-so, Soco-nuts, baby!
ダディデュデド どこなつ？ べいべー
Da-di-du-de-do, Doko-nuts? Baby!
かきくけココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke, Coco-nuts, baby!
サン！サン！サマータイム！yes！！！
Sun! Sun! Summer time! Yes!!!
どこ？そこ？あそこ？見つからないぜぃ？
Where? There? Over there? Can't find it anywhere?
パパイア マンゴー ココ☆ナツ！
Papaya, mango, coconut!
Huh?
Ah?
Are we in our hideout?
Yeah!
Wait, are the stairs here?
Yeah, they have stairs here!
Well, unless I invite them, of course.
But isn't this our first time showing it in 3D?
Yeah! That's true!
If you want to see our favorite part...
Wait, shut up!
We gotta go over here!
Look at all the candles! We have a lot of candles here!
Burning up!
But that's not the only one. There's more!
I have a favorite part too, you know.
If you look up there, what light through yonder window breaks?
Wow, the moon is beautiful tonight.
なにカッコつけてるですか？
What are you trying to sound cool for?
Well, about my favorite part... Look behind you!
This collection, it's all of my...
...stuff that we've collected over the years and stuff, right, right? You know?
And and her...
Yes! And her... what?
But also, we have our collars out here!
Wait, it's a dog collar!
And they're so cute! Wait, what? What? What's wrong? What?
Oh, wait! One Fubuki was wearing those?
Yeah, but they're right...
Fubuki?
Guys?
We're here!
I hear you boys, why do not see your bodies?
I hear you, boys, why do I not see your bodies?
I think they're hiding.
Got it!
No!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
You're on bone!
Dogs!
Arf! Arf!
Oh, they're so cute!
Wait a second.
Yeah, I hear voices coming from the dogs.
I think this might be FUWAMOCO?
Huh? What? What?
Wait, do you mean FUWAMOCO have been turned into Dobermans?
Oh, my god! What?
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, you know, I think they actually look more like Hellhounds like this.
Yeah, they're good girls! Give them a big pet.
Yeah, you'll see.
You're a good girl! Yes, you are.
Yeah, good girl! Good girl!
Wait, why are they Dobermans all of a sudden? What happened?
Hahaha! Hahaha!
Hehehe! Not so fluffy and fuzzy now, hoeh?
Pokey! Change us back down! We can't eat donuts like this!
That's why you wanna turn back? Hmph, whatever.
I'll give you one final trial! Clear it, and I'll restore them!
Mococo-chan! That means we can go back to normal!
Okay, everybody, help us, please! I guess we'll give you one donut for the rescue.
Just one? Donut- one each or... Hey! We kind of like you like this, though.
Pokey, what kind of challenge are you going to give us today?
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai!
Behold, the challenge before you!
Oh! The carpet has changed.
Wait, why do they have no faces? That's kind of scary.
Yeah, it is a little creepy. I like it.
Hehe, ever heard of Fukuwarai? It's this old-school Japanese game, lemme show you how it's played.
See those two giant faces? Their face parts are all scattered around.
Bijou and Shiori will be blindfolded and carry the face parts!
Oh, nice! Oh, yeah! Honestly, that sounds like fun.
Huh? We don't have to do anything?
Big bird, with your words alone, you must guide them. Lead them to place each piece and restore FUWAMOCO's face!
Me? Yeah, you.
Well, we're just going to be over here blindfolded. Yeah, we're just going to chill. Good luck. Okay, I'll do my best. No pressure.
No pressure at all! Good luck to you!
You've got 5 minutes. Better make it count!
Okay! Let's all say FUWAMOCO together!
Or not! Or not! Let's do it! Let's go! Yeah!
All right, ladies, so first plan of action, come on over, one on each side of me, pretty please.
Okay. And then I would like you to turn around.
Oh, okay. So, I have prepared for you blindfolds, so I'm going to go ahead and just, you can feel free to adjust them as you'd like.
But, uh, that way you won't be able to see anything since I have to direct you, so go ahead and turn back around.
I cannot see a thing.
Yes, perfect, that's exactly what we want.
All right. And then, uh, we're going to go ahead and start placing these things. So FUWAMOCO, my puppies, I'll do my best for you, okay?
You can do it! Oh, you're welcome! Let's do this! Let's do it!
Okay. And start!
Okay. So, what I'm going to do is I'm going to hand you guys each a piece and then I'm going to tell you where to go.
Go first, Shiori. So you're each going to do one face.
Okay. Okay.
So, uh, we're going to start that way. Which way?
Where am I? Where am I? What is this?
Shiori is just grabbing. I don't know what I'm grabbing.
Okay, so, uh, Shiori, walk to me. Just walk to some of my voice.
Oh, it's probably this way. This way? No. Yes, yes, this way, this way. Walk towards me.
Okay. If I accidentally grab something, I'm sorry.
Okay, grab onto this, this? Yes. Yes. Okay. Don't move.
Okay. Okay. Don't move! Don't move!
Bijou, I want you to walk to the sound of my voice, okay?
Where is the sound of your voice? Just right here. Right here.
Right, uh, your right, your right. Okay. Just a little right. Okay, forward.
Quickly! Okay, now come to me.
Where is yours? Uh, uh, uh.
Okay, so, uh, I want you to grab this. Oh, okay, I got it. Yes.
So pretty much where you are right now, uh, not you Shiori. Okay, Shiori, come forward a little bit.
This forward or this forward? The forward towards me.
This forward? Okay, that's too much, back up just a little bit. And then I want you to move uh
Your right? Your right? Right? Right? This is right! Left! Left! Okay, back up!
Okay, Mococo-chan, I don't know if this is going to work out. Place it down.
I felt strong, but now I'm regretting that. Place it down, Biboo. Oh, down.
Move it forward a little bit.
Ah, forward?
Okay.
And then can you straighten it out?
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Just a little bit more.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Okay, yeah.
And then can you just scoot the whole thing over to the right?
Scoot it? Scoot it?
No, left.
What about make sure that I put it in the same-- No, other way!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay. Next item.
Next item.
Stay right where you are. Stay right where you are.
I am here, my. I got you two. Okay, I got two, yeah.
I feel you two.
Do you have a... eyes?
I want you both, yes.
I want you both to walk backwards, okay?
Okay. My step.
Maybe straighten it out a little bit.
Woah, okay, that's definitely too high.
Okay, back? No, actually you're perfect where you are.
Wait, wait, wait!
You better get running.
I know, I'm perfect. Place it here.
One down.
Which one?
This one? No, you went too far!
No, we're going again.
What? Where are we going? This one's okay, right?
Yep. No, move it over to the right.
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right! Okay, okay. Place the other one.
I don't want-- I don't want to hit you like this. Okay, move it-- Please, core me.
This way? No.
Where am I? This way? Yeah, our face has to be like this for the game.
I did it!
Me?
Oh, dog.
Okay, people, come towards the sound of my voice.
Where is the sound of your voice?
I think just over here. Forward. Forward.
Okay, stop.
Uh now come this way a little bit. Turn this way!
Do you hear where I am?
Oh yes, yes.
Yeah, pretend, pretend you're in an immersion. Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect. Okay, stop, stop, stop.
Okay. Now I want you to turn a little bit this way.
Wait, this is the wrong way!
Like rotate your body! Rotate me!
Okay. So now I want you to place the one in your left hand down, okay? On the ground.
Like this?
Yeah, okay. Now I want you to walk slightly in this direction.
Just like crab walk.
See what ear I'm at.
Oh, yes.
Like an immersive game. Feeling like a game, people.
Okay. Place it down. Good, good, good.
Turn around. Both sides. Are we doing this right?
Shall we do it or what?
No, we have one minute. One more.
Okay. Okay, I'm done.
Okay. Now we won really, really good.
Yes, yes. So, people,
you're...
Walk this way.
Okay. Put it down.
Right there.
Wait, no, that's the wrong way. Pick it back up.
Walk. Opposite side. Okay!
Behind you.
Move backwards, backwards, backwards, backwards, backwards, backwards, backwards. Okay, down!
At least my face looks a bit better than your Sola.
Now, walk this way.
Which is this way?
Yeah, yeah. Now, walk uh to your left.
Wait, wait. I think you'll mess up. So, sorry.
This way! Left, left, left, this way! Yes. Okay, now forward.
Yes, forward.
I think we're going.
Forward. Yes. Now put it down.
So good.
Yeah, and listen please.
Okay. Fifteen seconds left.
Everyone? And...
Here you would make it look so perfect.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fifteen seconds. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it.
Oh, it's done.
Two, one!
Wow, nice!
Okay, I want you guys to turn on and around, and we're going to take off your blindfold so you can see how you did, okay?
Wait, which way is around?
This way.
This way? Yeah, yeah.
Well, let's take a look.
I bet we did great.
Not to look at it.
Yeah!
It's what?
Pokey, what do you think? Isn't it good?
Hey, Bijou, Shiori! You sure this is Fuwawa and Mococo?
Yeah, look at it.
So like Shior is a little...
No, no, no, it looks good.
We can make it better.
No, we don't, please.
This? No. We can have it, don't it's fine. I think it looks perfect. Why are you adjusting it?
I'm not changing anything. We're making it better!
It's perfect! It's better this way.
What am I with this over here?
I want to put it there. Don't touch my face! Put it like a...
Good, good, good!
Yes, perfect.
Yeah. The position you see to do it like this because I just wanted to see what it would look like a little lower.
This is not good.
Well, is it good enough to get changed back, Pokey?
Hmph, fine. I'll change them back!
Yay!
We can't fool Mococo anymore!
(Ha, ha, ha, ha)
Yeah, that's karma
Yeah, get down
Checkmate, I'm a superstar
Stay insane, but you rock with it, ah
Like 24/7, I'm a hot mess ya, love-hate
Get less boring, oh, my god
Homuran, batabata swing my shot, ah
Like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different
派手にぶちかまそう
Let's smash it with a bang!
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now, I can show ya how
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
No way, no way, yeah, way, yeah, way, yeah
"Good versus evil" is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party, just leave it to moi
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
That's karma, ta-da-ha-ha-ha
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some-ish, get it
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why're you running?
Bet ya think you're clever
Whatever
Talk about a "kumbaya"
フルボッコんボっちゃって
Beat 'em down to a pulp
欲求不満あがれ
Satisfy your desires
Ai dollar heart, get down, wink, sayonara saiko desu wa
Domestic
Dramatic
愛しき人々 この指とまれ
Beloved people, gather around my finger
ハートにハートはハイになって はじけてはじり捨てちゃえ
Hearts get high, burst and cast away shyness
叫びおどりほこれ激動的ショータイム よいしれてちょうだい
Scream, dance, and boast, tumultuous showtime, get intoxicated
道化のパラダイス 光り合う
Clown's paradise, shining together
感覚が共鳴共鳴
Senses resonating, resonating
Good vs. Evil, but I'm which one?
Just stuck here in the middle, that's not any fun
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
That's karma, ta-da-ha-ha-ha
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some-ish, get it
想像から創造
From imagination to creation
衝動から猛攻
From impulse to fierce attack
ほらあっという間に華麗に変身 変幻自在
Look, instantly transforming brilliantly, ever-changing
毒々しい本能
Poisonous instinct
喰らえ咆哮
Devour the roar
Talk about a "kumbaya", sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why're you running?
Bet ya think you're clever, whatever
Talk about a "kumbaya"
異世界クィン スウィッチチューニングマイナス カラフルにカコフォニー
Isekai queen, switch tuning minus, colorful cacophony
歪で優雅にハチャメチャ Welcome to Miss Fortune's game
Twisted, elegant, and chaotic, welcome to Miss Fortune's game
It's just Prisoner, remember?
It doesn't matter, it's gonna sound great, right?
Yeah!
And if you want to find out, don't go anywhere,
'cause you'll be redirected to the music video right after this stream!
Yeah!
Let's go!
And guess what? We're also going to premiere the new song right after this!
Yeah!
Let's go!
All right, everybody, are you ready?
Places, places! Places!
Okay.
Locked away where nightmares keep you awake,
You’ll be safe within my crushing embrace
You’re all mine, all mine
You’ll never escape...
Wayward soul, I’ll wrap you up in darkness that consumes you whole,
hold you in my labyrinth of walls
Lost in the depths that swallow you, where just your shadows follow you
Always churning in the deep, I won’t let you sleep
You don’t need your dreams now that you belong to me
Throw them all away, you’re too frail to be free
You will always be my lovely prisoner
Are you shaking?
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
You can only be mine
Poor little prisoner
Are you breaking?
My chains will bind you here forever,
Stay here for all time
In tenebris
in frigore
in carcere
Close your eyes, go deeper in the emptiness that plagues your mind,
let my dark envelop your light
I will keep you safe and sound, hear the blissful silence all around
I’ll drag you down below, never let you go
Everything you’ve been, the transgressions of your past;
Throw them all away, let me hold you at last
My lovely prisoner
What’s the matter?
You’re never leaving, you are mine forever
Got to keep you right here
Poor, helpless prisoner
Did you shatter?
Why are you grieving your ambitions? Let them disappear
I can hear your plea, reaching desperately, but I’ll never, ever set you free
Stay with me...
My lovely prisoner
Are you shaking?
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
You can only be mine
Poor little prisoner
Are you breaking?
My chains will bind you here forever,
Stay here for all time
In tenebris
in frigore
in carcere
Yeah!
That was our new song, "Prisoner"!
What did you think of the track, huh? Hot song, huh? Yeah!
Okay, and let's all move on to the second piece of exciting news, getting close, girls!
Yeah!
Hololive English Advent 2nd Anniversary Celebration!
First up, we have the framed art board.
It's a large illustration board framed beautifully.
The luxurious frame features our logo with foil stamping for the extra shine. It's a perfect item to decorate your home and to enjoy looking at every single day,
so you can see all of us together, just like we should be.
Well, next up, we have a sticker set from 2024 Halloween version!
Five different designs, and it includes the VR Chat design released for Halloween,
plus a three-piece sticker set featuring each Advent member's original design.
And then you can put them on your phone, stick them on your PC, and have fun with them!
Yeah!
All right, next up, we got the connecting charm!
With all these charms that can actually connect!
What's awesome is that all these charms can actually connect!
So,
choose each other,
you can mix and match for all kinds of different ways, right?
And have fun!
Yeah!
Finally, we've got the Varsity Jacket!
Wow!
It's got the Advent logo on the back,
and Poki is embroidered
on the front test day, too!
Wow!
And guess what?
What?
You can actually attach those charms
I just showed you
on the zipper of the jacket, too!
You know, it's a cool item that you can rock
both in your everyday life and at events, too!
Yeah!
And guess what?
What?
It's happening right now!
The merch just dropped at the Hololive Official Shop!
Now!
Hey guys, notice that guy showing up on the bottom
of the bottom left, left of the YouTube screen,
go ahead and click it
to shop your favorites, okay?
This was such a wonderful day together.
We had so much fun!
You guys probably were running
from justice at the time.
Yeah, but that's typical Friday.
Were we really worried?
No, better luck next time, Justice.
As if you could ever catch us!
We are sentinels!
Yeah! Don't forget that!
We've been together for two years now!
Can you believe it?
Lots of memories.
Yeah, lots of memories,
and we're looking forward
to all of the next years together.
Year three!
Year four!
Year five!
Year six!
Yeah! Hell yeah!
Together forever!
Yes! Together forever!
Bros before Riding Adventures!